<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE legalnotice
[
  <!ENTITY % entities SYSTEM "entity-decl.ent">
    %entities;
]>
<!-- Converted by suse-upgrade version 1.1 -->
<!--
     Please keep this document neatly formatted, because a text version
     for LICENSE.txt is created from this source. That means only the
     xml tags will be stripped, the rest of the formatting will appear
     in the txt file as is.
-->
<legalnotice xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" version="5.0">
 <para>
  All content is copyright &copy; 2006&ndash;
<?dbtimestamp format="Y"?>
  SUSE LLC. All rights reserved.
 </para>
 <para>
  Legal Notice
 </para>
 <para>
  This manual is protected under SUSE intellectual property rights. By
  reproducing, duplicating or distributing this manual you explicitly agree
  to conform to the terms and conditions of this license agreement.
 </para>
 <para>
  This manual may be freely reproduced, duplicated and distributed either as
  such or as part of a bundled package in electronic and/or printed format,
  provided however that the following conditions are fulfilled:
 </para>
 <simplelist>
  <member>
   That this copyright notice and the names of authors and contributors appear
   clearly and distinctively on all reproduced, duplicated and distributed
   copies. That this manual, specifically for the printed format, is reproduced
   and/or distributed for noncommercial use only. The express authorization of
   Novell, Inc must be obtained prior to any other use of any manual or part
   thereof.
  </member>
 </simplelist>
 <para>
  For SUSE or Novell trademarks, see the Novell Trademark and Service Mark
  list
  <link xlink:href="http://www.novell.com/company/legal/trademarks/tmlist.html"/>.
  All other third party trademarks are the property of their respective
  owners. A trademark symbol (&reg;, &trade; etc.) denotes a SUSE or
  Novell trademark; an asterisk (*) denotes a third party trademark.
 </para>
 <para>
  All information found in this book has been compiled with utmost attention
  to detail. However, this does not guarantee complete accuracy. Neither
  SUSE LLC, SUSE LINUX Products GmbH, the authors, nor the translators shall
  be held liable for possible errors or the consequences thereof.
 </para>
</legalnotice>
